Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Drawing of Stephen Foster by Janet Dexter (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11340)
- Page 2 of letter from Stephen Foster to Morrison, July 8, 1853 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11341)
- Page two of the manuscript for "The Abolition Show" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11342)
- Page two of letter from Stephen Foster to Morrison, Oct. 22, 1858 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11343)
- painting of Foster by Marie Goth (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11344)
- Title page for The Atheneaum Collection of Hymns and Tunes, 1863 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11345)
- Title page for "The Social Orchestra", 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11346)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to William, Jr., November 9, 1840 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11347)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to William, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11348)
- Tintype of Stephen Foster and George Cooper (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11349)
- Colorized tintype of Stephen Foster and George Cooper (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11349.02)
- Autographed carte de visite of George Cooper (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11349.01)
- Telegram sent by George Cooper to Morrison Foster after Stephen's death, January 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11350)
- Letter from George Cooper to Morrison Foster, January 12, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11351)
- Side by side images of Stephen Foster's hospital bill and an inventory of his belongings, January 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11352)
- Page in songbook showing "Tell Me of the Angels, Mother" by Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11353)
- Page from Davidson's Universal Melodist showing "Open Thy Lattice, Love" (NOT by Foster) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11354)
- Title page for Morrison Foster's Biography, Songs and Musical Compositions, 1896 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11355)
- Cover page for "Long Ago Day" and "This Rose Will Remind You" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11356)
- Title pages of The Love and Sentimental Songster and The American Song Book (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11357)
- Scrap of paper found in Foster's wallet reading "Dear Friends and Gentle Hearts", 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11358)
- Side by side broadsides of "Gentle Annie" and "Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11359)
- Side by side broadsides of "Beautiful Dreamer" and "Bring My Brother Back to Me" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11360)
- First page of the manuscript for Stephen Foster's "The Wife" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11361)
- Second page of Foster's manuscript for "The Wife" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11362)
- Side by side broadsides of "Uncle Ned" and "Massa's in the Cold Ground" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11363)
- Page 3 of manuscript of "Old Folks at Home Variations," by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11364)
- Page 5 of Foster's manuscript for "Old Folks at Home Variations" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11365)
- Page 1 of Foster's manuscript for "Old Folks at Home Variations" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11366)
- Page 2 of Foster's manuscript of "Old Folks at Home Variations" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11367)
- Side by side broadsides of "Bob-Tailed Nag" and "Fairy Belle" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11368)
- Second page of Foster's manuscript of "Linda Has Departed" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11369)
- Manuscript entitled "Serenade" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11370)
- Manuscript entitled "Fourth" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11371)
- First page for Foster's manuscript for "Sadly to Mine Heart Appealing" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11372)
- Second page of Foster's manuscript for "Sadly to Mine Heart Appealing" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11373)
- Page three of the manuscript for Foster's "Linda Has Departed" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11374)
- Letter from George Cooper to Robert Coster, March 6, 1919 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11375)
- First page for Foster's manuscript for "Linda Has Departed" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11376)
- Title page for the British edition of "My Old Kentucky Home" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11388)
- Page two of "My Old Kentucky Home, Good-Night!" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11389)
- Page three of "My Old Kentucky Home, Good-Night!" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11390)
- Page four of "My Old Kentucky Home, Good-Night!" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11391)
- Page five of "My Old Kentucky Home, Good-Night!" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11392)
- Sheet music cover for "Poor Old Joe" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11393)
- First Edition sheet music cover for "Willie, My Brave" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11394)
- Sheet music cover for "Oh Susanna" with a handwritten notation that it was deposited in the Copyright Office on Feb. 28, 1848 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11395)
- Sheet music cover for Foster's "Willie We Have Missed You" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11396)
- Sheet music cover for "Under the Willow She's Sleeping" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11397)
- Sheet music cover for "Gentle Lena Clare" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11398)
- Sheet music cover for "Old Dog Tray" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11399)
- Sheet Music cover for "Old Black Joe" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11400)
- Cover for "The Sparkling Stream" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11401)
- Foster's leather purse and the money found in it when he died (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11402)
- Pages FOR-FOU in Stephen Foster's dictionary (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11403)
- Page in Cincinnati Directory of 1849-1850 showing Josiah Kirby's name (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11404)
- Pages 44 and 45 of Foster's account book showing accounts from Firth and Pond (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11405)
- Pages 46 and 47 of Foster's account book showing accounts from Firth and Pond (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11406)
- Pages of Foster's account book showing accounts from Firth and Pond (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11407)
- Pages from Foster's account book showing "Receipts on Music" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11408)
- Foster's account book pages 42-43 showing the continuation of "Receipts on Music" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11409)
- Firth, Pond, and Company ad on page 35 of "The Musical World and Times" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11413)
- Cover of Charles Grobe's arrangement for "Nancy Till" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11414)
- Title page of English edition of "Farewell My Lilly Dear" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11415)
- title page of English edition of "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11416)
- title page of E. J. Westrop's arrangement of "Nancy Till" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11417)
- Page 50 of "Christy's Minstrels' Banjo Tutor" showing "Nancy Till," credited to S.C. Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11418)
- Title page of the first edition of "Old Folks at Home" showing E. P. Christy as composer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11419)
- First page (number 3) of first edition of "Old Folks at Home" showing E. P. Christy as composer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11420)
- Second page (number 4) of first edition of "Old Folks at Home" showing E. P. Christy as composer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11421)
- Third page (number 5) of 1st edition of "Old Folks at Home" showing E. P. Christy as composer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11422)
- Title page of "Jim Crow Jubilee," Reed edition of "Old Uncle Ned" by Foster, arranged by A. Clapp (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11423)
- Title page of "Ellen Bayne" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11424)
- Sheet music cover for the first edition of "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11425)
- Sheet music cover for the first edition of "Gentle Annie" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11426)
- title page of 1st edition of "My Old Kentucky Home, Good Night" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11427)
- Title page of first edition of "Maggie by My Side" by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11428)
- Sheet music cover for Foster's "Linger in Blissful Repose" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11429)
- Sheet music cover for Foster's "Beautiful Dreamer" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11430)
- Sheet music cover for the first edition of Foster's "Fairy-Belle" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11431)
- Sheet music cover for the first edition for Foster's "The Glendy Burk" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11432)
- Sheet music cover for Foster's "Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11433)
- Enlargement of Firth, Pond and Company ad on page 35 of "The Musical World and Times" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11434)
- Page in Cincinnati Directory of 1849-1850, showing Stephen Foster's name (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11435)
- page in Cincinnati Directory of 1849-1850 showing Dunning Foster's name (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11436)
- page in Cincinnati Directory of 1849-1850 showing Stephen Foster's name (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11437)
- Stone monument erected at the source of the Suwanee River (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11457)
- Entrance to Foster Hall showing the plaque with the building's name and "Let No Discordant Note Enter Here" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11483)
- interior of Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11484)
- Close up of plaque outside of Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11485)
- Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11490)
- Cover of Waters' Choral Harp for Sunday School (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11526)
- Title page and interior of front cover for Waters Choral Harp (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11527)
- Pages 44 and 45 of Waters Choral Harp with "The Beautiful Shore," music by Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11528)
- Morrison Foster as an old man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11546)
- Foster ambrotype, from carte de visite (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11588)
- Portrait of Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11593)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 1, folio 1 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11599.01)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 2, folio 1 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11599.02)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" sketchbook page 3, 2 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11599.03)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 4, folio 2 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11600)
- Manuscript of "In the Eye Abides the Heart" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 5, folio 3 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11600.01)
- Manuscript of "In the Eye Abides the Heart" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 6, folio 3 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11601)
- Manuscript of "My Hopes Have Departed Forever" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 7, folio 4 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11602)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" sketchbook page 8, 4 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11602.01)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 9, folio 5 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11603)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 10, folio 5 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11604)
- Manuscript of "Laura Lee" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 11, folio 6 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11605)
- Manuscript "Ah! My Child" sketchbook page 12, 6 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11605.01)
- Manuscript of "Ah! My Child" sketchbook page 13, 7 rector (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11605.02)
- Manuscript of "Old Folks at Home" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 14, folio 7 verso. Margin inscription "Cramer, Beale & Co. music publishers 201 Regent Street & 67 Conduit Street London)") (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11606)
- Manuscript of "Willie My Brave"from Foster's sketchbook, p. 15, folio 8 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11606.01)
- Manuscript of "Willie My Brave" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 16, folio 8 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11606.02)
- Manuscript of "Willie My Brave" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 17, folio 9 recto. (loose, formerly attached to endpaper) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11606.03)
- Manuscript of "Willie My Brave" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 18, folio 9 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11607)
- Manuscript of (Campaign Song of 1852) from Foster's sketchbook, p. 20, folio 10 verso. End of first gathering (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11608.01)
- Manuscript of (Campaign Song of 1852) from Foster's sketchbook, p. 21, folio 11 recto. (loose, formerly attached to leaf 22) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11608.02)
- Manuscript of (Campaign Song of 1852) from Foster's sketchbook, p. 22, folio 11 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11608.03)
- Manuscript of (Campaign Song of 1852) from Foster's sketchbook, p. 23, folio 12 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11608.04)
- Manuscript of "Willie My Brave" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 19, folio 10 recto. (loose, formerly attached to endpaper) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11608)
- Manuscript of "Old Folks at Home" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 24, folio 12 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11609)
- Manuscript of "Old Folks at Home" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 25, folio 13 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11610)
- Manuscript of "Farewell My Lily Dear" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 26, folio 13 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11611)
- Manuscript of "Farewell My Lily Dear" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 27, folio 14 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11612)
- Manuscript of "Farewell My Lily Dear" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 28, folio 14 verso. (below: 4 lines of another lyric, partly erased) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11613)
- Manuscript of "Brudder Bones" from Foster's sketchbook p. 30, 15 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11614.01)
- Manuscript of "Brudder Bones" from Foster's sketchbook p. 31, 16 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11614.02)
- Manuscript of "Brudder Bones" from Foster's sketchbook p. 32, 16 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11614.03)
- Manuscript of "Brudder Bones" from Foster's sketchbook p. 33, 17 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11614.04)
- Manuscript of "Blow Light Ye Wandering Zephyrs" (at top) "Brudder Bones" (at bottom) both by Foster -- unpublished manuscripts from "Sketch Book," p. 29, folio 15 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11614)
- Manuscript of "Massa's in de Cold Ground" from Foster's sketchbook p. 34, folio 17 verso. (music notation at top) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11615)
- Manuscript of "Maggie by My Side" (version: "Fanny by My Side") from Foster's sketchbook p. 36, folio 18 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11616.01)
- Manuscript of "Maggie by My Side" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 37, folio 19 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11616.02)
- Manuscript of "Maggie by My Side" from Foster's sketchbook, p. 38, folio 19 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11616.03)
- Manuscript of "The Hour for Thee and Me" from Foster's sketchbook p. 39, folio 20 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11616.04)
- Manuscript of "Massa's in de Cold Ground" from Foster's sketchbook p. 35, 18 recto. (music notation underlaid with lyrics at top) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11616)
- Manuscript of "Maggie by My Side" from Foster's sketchbook p. 40, folio 20 verso, 2nd verse (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11617)
- Sketchbook page 42, 21 verso, "While the Flowrets Gently Tremble" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11618.01)
- Sketchbook page 43, 22 recto "I Have Woo'd Thee Never Deeming" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11618.02)
- Sketchbook page 44, 22 verso "Massa's in de Cold Ground" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11618.03)
- Sketchbook page 45, 23 recto "Massa's in de Cold Ground" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11618.04)
- Sketchbook page 41, 21 recto "Maggie's by My Side" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11618)
- Sketchbook page 47, 24 recto "Massa's in de Cold Ground" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11619.01)
- Manuscript of "Massa's in de Cold Ground" from Foster's sketchbook p. 46, folio 23 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11619)
- Manuscript "From the Wilmington's" Foster's sketchbook, page 49, 25 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11620.01)
- Manuscript of "Massa's in de Cold Ground" by Foster, sketchbook, p. 48, folio 24 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11620)
- Manuscript "My Old Kentucky Home" sketchbook p. 50, 25 v (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11621)
- Manuscript "Old Schoolmarm" sketchbook page 52, 26 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11622.01)
- Manuscript "Old Partner of Our Youthful Mirth" sketchbook page 53, 27 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11622.02)
- Manuscript "Poor Uncle Tom Good Night" ("My Old Kentucky Home") sketchbook page 51, 26 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11622)
- Manuscript "The Village Bells" page 55, 28 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11623.01)
- Manuscript "My Own Sweet Avonmoor" sketchbook page 56, 28 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11623.02)
- Manuscript "Village Maiden" page 54, 27 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11623)
- Manuscript "Old Dog Tray" sketchbook page 58, 29 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11624)
- Manuscript "Old Dog Tray" sketchbook page 59, 30 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11625)
- Manuscript "Old Dog Tray" sketchbook page 60, 30 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11626)
- Manuscript "Old Memories" sketchbook page 62, 31v (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11627.01)
- Manuscript "Old Memories" sketchbook page 63, 32 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11627.02)
- Manuscript "Old Dog Tray" sketchbook 61, 31 rector (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11627)
- Manuscript "Of Woman with Her Smiles and Tears" page 65, 33 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11628.01)
- Manuscript "Thoughts Suggested on Being Asked to Sing at a Banquet" sketchbook page 66, 33 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11628.02)
- Manuscript "Old Memories" page 64, 32 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11628)
- Manuscript "Little Ella" sketchbook page 68, 34 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11629.01)
- Manuscript "Little Ella" sketchbook page 69, 35 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11629.02)
- Manuscript for "Lines Suggested on Being Invited to Sing at a Banquet" sketchbook page 67, 34 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11629)
- Manuscript "Ellen Bayne" page 71, 36 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11630.01)
- Manuscript "Ellen Bayne" sketchbook page 72, 36 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11630.02)
- Manuscript "Ellen Bayne" sketchbook page 73, 37 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11630.03)
- Manuscript "Little Ella" sketchbook page 70, 35 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11630)
- Manuscript "Ellen Bayne" sketchbook page 74, 37 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11631)
- Manuscript "Willie We Have Missed You" page 76, 38 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11632.01)
- Manuscript "Willie We Have Missed You" sketchbook page 77, 39 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11632.02)
- Manuscript "Willie We Have Missed You" sketchbook page 78, 39 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11632.03)
- Manuscript "Willie We Have Missed You" page 79, 40 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11632.04)
- Manuscript "Ellen Bayne" sketchbook page 75, 38 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11632)
- Manuscript "Willie We Have Missed You" page 80, 40 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11633)
- Manuscript "Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair" sketchbook page 82, 41 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11634.01)
- Manuscript "Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair" sketchbook page 83, 42 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11634.02)
- Manuscript "Willie We Have Missed You" page 81, 41 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11634)
- Manuscript "Hoboken" sketchbook page 85, 43 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11635.01)
- Manuscript "Old Partner of Our Youthful Mirth" sketchbook page 86, 43 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11635.02)
- Manuscript "How Shall I Woo The" sketchbook page 87, 44 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11635.03)
- Manuscript "Be Not Downhearted" sketchbook page 88, 44 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11635.04)
- Manuscript "Ah, My Child" sketchbook page 89, 45 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11635.05)
- Manuscript "When the Bowl Goes Round" sketchbook page 90, 45 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11635.06)
- Manuscript "Jeanie with the Light Brown Hair" sketchbook page 84, 42 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11635)
- Manuscript "Molly Dear" sketchbook page 92, 46 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.01)
- Manuscript "Molly Dear" sketchbook page 93, 47 rector (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.02)
- Manuscript "Molly Dear" sketchbook page 94, 47 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.03)
- Manuscript "Molly Dear" sketchbook page 95, 48 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.04)
- Manuscript "Molly Dear" sketchbook page 96, 48 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.05)
- Manuscript "Come with Thy Sweet Voice Again" sketchbook page 97, 49 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.06)
- Manuscript "Come with Thy Sweet Voice Again" sketchbook page 98 49 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.07)
- Manuscript "There's Many a Robin, a Big Bellied Bear" sketchbook page 99, 50 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.08)
- Manuscript "A Robin Once Sat" sketchbook page 100, 50 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.09)
- Manuscript "The Robin," sketchbook page 101, 51 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.1)
- Manuscript "A Robin Sits in a Sycamore Tree" sketchbook page 102, 51 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.11)
- Manuscript "But Creeping and Flying are Different Things" sketchbook page 103, 52 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636.12)
- Manuscript "Parting" sketchbook 91, 46 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11636)
- Manuscript "The Robin and the Butterfly," page 104, 52 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11637)
- Manuscript "Come Like a Spirit that Dwells" sketchbook page 106, 53 verso. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11638.01)
- Manuscript for "The Robin and the Butterfly" manuscript page 105, 53, recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11638)
- Manuscript for "Duet" sketchbook page 108, 54 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11639.01)
- Manuscript "Hard Times" sketchbook page 109, 55 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11639.02)
- Manuscript "Hard Times" sketchbook page 110, 55 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11639.03)
- Manuscript "Hard Times" sketchbook page 111, 56 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11639.04)
- Manuscript for "Come with Thy Sweet Voice Again" sketchbook page 107, 54 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11639)
- Manuscript "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" sketchbook page 113, 57 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11640.01)
- Manuscript "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming" sketchbook page 114, 57 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11640.02)
- Manuscript "Come Where My Love Lies Dreaming," page 115, 58 recto (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11640.03)
- Manuscript "Some Folks," sketchbook page 116, 58 verso (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 11640.04)